You know, one of the most common things going on right now is foreclosure repos.
Uh, most of my clients are facing custody battles
or something going on with their kids.
And my first step when I teach into all of my mentees that learn under me
is to always get a trust. Get a trust.
Get a trust. Get a trust.
I cannot stress it enough to have a trust.
If you don't have a trust,
the state owns your kids. That house you don't truly own yet.
You really don't truly own it
because people don't even understand that you're just a tenant of occupancy.
Even when you signed on a house,
they don't care about a mortgage.
They don't care about that payment.
You're just a tenant. And when they wanna go for clothes on it and take it back,
they can because you did not protect your house.
You did not accept the deed.
You did not convey the property.
Your house is unprotected.
Your kids is unprotected. Your cars are unprotected.
So that repo can happen at any given moment.
But when you get a trust and you protect your assets,
who's stopping you? Who's,
who's checking for you? Who's checking for you? Get a trust.